Guide to the Andrew F. Smith Collection of Cookery Ephemera MSS.295
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Cookery Ephemera, 1798-2009
  - Rumford Chemical Works, circa 1876-1920s, 1941 (Box 34, Folder 9-14)
    Rumford. Rumford Book and Recipes and Recipes for Using Rumford Yeast Powder and Horsford's Bread Preparation. Providence, RI: Rumford Chemical Works, undated.
    Rumford. Haxworth, Lily, comp. Household Hand Book Containing Reliable Hints and Suggestions for the Household. Providence, RI: Rumford Chemical Works, undated.
    Rumford. Beeks, Henrietta C., comp. Rumford Cook Book. Providence, RI: Rumford Chemical Works, 1914.
    Rumford. A Few Choice Recipes; Try Them. Providence, RI: Rumford Chemical Works, undated.
    Rumford. Farmer, Fannie Merritt, Lily Haxworth Wallace and Mildred Maddocks, comp. Rumford Home Recipes. Providence, RI: Rumford Chemical Works, 1915.
    Rumford. Rumford Receipt Book. Providence, RI: Rumford Chemical Works, after 1909.
    Rumford. Maddocks, Mildred. Every Day Dishes. Providence, RI: Rumford Chemical Works, 1911.
    Rumford. Baker, Elizabeth Ann. Magic Muffins! Twenty-Three Recipes. Rumford, RI: Rumford Chemical Works, 1941.
  - The Rumford Company, circa 1919-1940s (Box 34, Folder 15-16, Box 35, Folder 1)
    Rumford. Wallace, Lily Haxworth, comp. Rumford Common Sense Cook Book. Rumford, RI: Rumford Company, undated.
    Rumford. Splint, Sarah Field. The Rumford Modern Methods of Cooking. Providence, RI: The Rumford Co., undated.
    Rumford. Hill, Janet McKenzie, comp. The Rumford Way of Cookery and Household Economy. Providence, RI: Rumford Chemical Works, undated.
    Rumford. Giving Delicacy and Flavor to Daily Cooking; 64 New Uses for Rumford All-Phosphate Baking Powder in Daily Cooking. Rumford, RI: The Rumford Company, 1931.
    Rumford. Rumford Everyday Cook Book for the Housekeeper and Student. Providence, RI: The Rumford Co., undated.
  - Russell-Miller Milling Company, 1922, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    Russell-Miller Milling Co. Golden Glow; Yellow Corn Flour; An Excellent Wheat Flour Substitute. Minneapolis, MN: Russell Miller Milling Co., undated.
    Russell-Miller Milling Co. More and Better Bread; Your Money Back Unless Occident Makes Better Bread. Minneapolis, MN: Russell-Miller Milling Co., 1922.
  - Rutherford Food Corporation, circa 1950s (Box 35, Folder 3)
    Rutherford Food Corporation. Rutherford's Hypower Brand Mexican Foods. Kansas City, MO: Rutherford Food Corporation, undated.
  - Sam Huddleston, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Sam Thompson Distilling Company, circa 1910-1920s (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - The S. A. Mullikin Company, 1907 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    S. A. Mullikin Co. The Best Yet Cook Book. Marietta, OH: S. A. Mullikin Co., 1907.
  - Samuel F. Prenzel--Oatena, circa 1850s (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Sanitary Dairy Company, 1937 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    Sanitary Dairy Company. Selected Recipes Featuring Salad & Cooking Cream. Chicago, IL: Jefferson Advertising Bureau, Inc., 1937.
  - Sanitas Nut Food Company, Limited, circa 1900 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    Sanitas Nut Food Co., Ltd. Sanitas Nut Preparations and Specialities. Battle Creek, MI: Sanitas Nut Food Co., Ltd., undated.
  - The Saratoga Liquor House, circa 1900 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Sargent & Company, 1902 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    Sargent & Company. Gem Chopper Cook Book. New York, NY: Sargent & Company, 1902.
    Sargent & Company. Gem Chopper Cook Book. New Haven, CT: Sargent & Company, 1902.
  - Saville, Somes & Company, 1889 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Scandia Fish Company, 1917 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    Scandia Fish Company. "Here's the Chance You've Been Looking For." Broadside. Duluth, MN: Scandia Fish Co., 1917.
  - Schlotterbeck & Foss Company, circa 1900 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    Foss' Pure Flavoring Extracts. "Dainty Dishes" with recipes written by Mrs. D. A. Lincoln. Boston, MA: Foss' Pure Flavoring Extracts, undated.
    Schlotterbeck & Foss Co. Lincoln, Mrs. D. A., Mrs. Carrie M. Dearborn and Miss Anna Borrows. Sixteen Dainty Desserts. Portland, ME: Schlotterbeck, & Foss Co., undated.
  - Schumacher Brothers, Inc., circa 1920s (Box 35, Folder 15)
    Schumacher Bros, Inc. Chateau Brands Foods of Quality from All Parts of the World. San Francisco, CA: Schumacher Bros, Inc., undated.
  - Scott, Anna Lee, circa 1940s (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Scott, Mrs. Anna B., 1936 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - The Sealshipt Oyster System, circa 1900 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Sealtest, Inc., 1939 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    Sealtest. The Sealtest Food Adviser. Radio City, NY: Sealtest Inc., 1939.
  - The Sears & Nichols Canning Company, circa 1910-1920s (Box 35, Folder 20)
    Sears & Nichols Canning Co. Sugar Loaf Sue's Recipes. Chillicothe, OH: Sears & Nichols Canning Co., undated.
  - Sears, Roebuck & Company, circa 1940-1950s (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Seneca County Courier--Mulliken & Mumford, 1848 (Box Shared Fales 002, Folder 14)
  - "Serendipity", 2007 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    Video news feature on Morton A. Meyers' Happy Accidents: Serenditpity in the Modern Medical Breakthrough.
  - Seven-Up Company, 1957 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    Seven-Up Co. You're Really Cooking when You're Cooking with Seven-Up. St. Louis, MO: Seven-Up Co., 1957.
  - Seville Packing Company, 1905 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    Seville Packing Co. Salads: How to Make & Serve Them. New York, NY: The Seville Packing Co., 1905.
  - S. F. Baker Company, 1935 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    S. F. Baker Co. Useful Suggestions. Keokuk, IA: S. F. Baker Co., 1935.
  - Sheffield Farms, circa 1920s (Box 35, Folder 26)
    Slawson, Decker Co. Sheffield Farms. New York, NY: Slawson, Decker Co., undated.
  - Shepard Hardware Company, circa 1850s (Box 35, Folder 27)
    Shepard Hardware Co. Queen City Receipt Book: The Celebrated Collection of Prize Receipts for Desserts, Ice Creams, Fruit Ices, Sherbets, Jellies, Puddings &c. Buffalo, NY: Shepard Hardware Co., undated.
  - Shields Date Gardens, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    Shields Date Gardens. Shields Date Gardens. Indio, CA: publisher unknown, 1962.
  - S. H. Morgan, 1861-1862 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Sidle, Fletcher & Holmes Company, 1885 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    Holmes Co. Cook Book. Minneapolis, MN: H. W. Fletcher Holmes Co., 1885.
  - Simmons, Adelma Grenier, circa 1970s (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Simmons Hardware Company, Inc., circa 1900 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Sioux Honey Association, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    Sioux Honey Association. Sue Bee Honey Magic Recipes. Sioux City, IA: Sioux Honey Association, 1974.
  - Skinner, H. Burchstead, circa 1855 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Skookum Apples, 1917 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Sloan, Dr. Earl S., 1901 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Smith & Adams--William P. Mattoon, 1880 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - The Smith Medicated Prune Company, circa 1850s (Box 36, Folder 9)
    Smith Medicated Prune Company. Smith's Medicated Prunes. Hartford, CT: Smith Medicated Prune Company, undated.
  - Smith & Swinney, Chemists, Etc., 1867 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    Smith & Swinney. The House-Keeper's Guide and Everybody's Hand-Book. Fourth Edition. Cincninnati: Smith & Swinney, 1867.
  - Snyder & Steepleton Manufacturers, 1893 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Southern Comfort Corporation, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Southern Laboratory Kitchens, 1936 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    Southern Laboratory Kitchens. 100 Centennial Recipes Celebrating 100 Years of Progressive Flour Milling in Texas. Dallas, TX: Southern Laboratory Kitchens, 1936.
  - Southern Pacific, circa 1950s (Box 36, Folder 14)
    Southern Pacific. Our Dinning Car Recipes. Place of publication unknown: Southern Pacific, circa 1950s.
  - The Speculum Press-- Simple Cooking, Vol. I, No. 1, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Spice Islands Company--Specialty Food & Beverage Sales, Inc., 1950, circa 1990s (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Spratt's Patent Ltd., circa 1880 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Spry Shortening, circa 1950s, 1970s (Box 36, Folder 17)
    Lever Brothers Company. Re-use Kitchen Fat Tricolator Filt-r-fat. New York, NY: Lever Brothers Company, undated.
  - Squires, Sherry & Galusha, circa 1860s (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - S. Sternau & Company, 1895, 1906 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    S. Sternau & Co. The Uses of the Chafing Dish. Place of publication unknown: S. Sternau & Co., 1895.
    S. Sternau & Co. Sternau Chafing Dish Recipes. Place of publication unknown: S. Sternau Co., 1906.
  - Staib, Inc.--The City Tavern, circa 2007-2009 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Staley's, circa 1930s (Box 36, Folder 20)
    Staley's. Staley's Selected Recipes and Menus. Place of publication unknown: publisher unknown, undated.
  - Standard Brands, Ltd., circa 1910-1920s (Box 36, Folder 21)
    Standard Brands Ltd, Gillett Products. Presto!; The Magic Baking Powder Cook Book. Montreal, Toronto and Winnipeg, Canada: Standard Brands Limited, Gillett Products, undated.
  - Standard Brands Inc., 1932-1950 (Box 36, Folder 22-23)
    Standard Brands. Royal Cook Book. New York, NY: Standard Brands, Inc., 1932.
    Standard Brands. Royal Cook Book. New York, NY: Standard Brands, Inc., 1935.
    Standard Brands. Here are the Cakes America Loves–Royal Cakes Made with Royal Cream of Tartar Baking Powder. New York, NY: Standard Brands, 1950.
    Standard Brands. A Guide to Royal Success in Baking; Royal Baking Powder. Place of publication unknown: Standard Brands, Inc., 1939.
  - The Standard Lighting Company, circa 1890s (Box 36, Folder 24)
    Standard Lighting Company. Cooking Made Easy by Using Gas. Cleveland, OH: The Standard Lighting Co., undated.
  - Standard Oil Company of California; Standard Oil Company of Indiana, 1944 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    Standard of California. How to Preserve Victory Garden Vegetables. Place of publication unknown: Standard of California, undated.
  - Stanton & Company Incorporated, 1911 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    Stanton & Company. Catalogue. Spring 1911. Chicago, IL: Stanton & Company, 1911.
  - Starr Ford, M.D., circa 1900 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - State Fish Exchange--California Department of Agriculture, 1928 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - State of New York--Canal Department, 1853, 1860 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Stephen F. Whitman & Son, Inc., 1923 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Stereoscopic Photograph Cards, 1892, 1905 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    "Golly! Dis am Paradise," [African American Children with Watermelon]. New York, NY: Underwood & Underwood, 1892.
  - Stickney & Poor Spice Company, circa 1892 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    Stickney & Poor Spice Co. Stickney & Poor's Extracts...Mustards...Spices...Cream Tartar Are the Best. Place of publication unknown: Stickney & Poor Spice Co., undated.
  - St. Louis Stamping Company, circa 1877 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    St. Louis Stamping Company. The Granite Iron Ware Cook Book; How to Cook. St. Louis, MO: St. Louis Stamping Company, circa 1877.
  - Stokley-Van Camp, Inc., circa 1970s (Box 37, Folder 7)
    Stokley-Van Camp, Inc. Mini-Menus for Singles and Doubles. Indianapolis, IN: Stokley-Van Camp, Inc., undated.
  - Stormont Selected Seafood, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Sturdivant Packing Company, 1924 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    Sturdivant Packing Company. Old Virginia Brunswick Stew. Brownsville, TN: Sturdivant Packing Company, undated.
  - Stutzen Der Hausfrau, 1898, 1915 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Sugar Research, 1867, 1900-1930s (Box 37, Folder 11, Box Shared Fales 003, Folder 5)
    American Sugar Refining Co. Festive Domino Sugar Recipes. Place of publication unknown: The American Sugar Refining Company, undated.
    Godchaux Sugars. The Story of Godchaux's Pure Cane Sugar. New Orleans, LA: Godchaux Sugars, Inc., 1933.
    Revere Sugar. "Alice Bradley says." (Ephemera - single sheet) Place of publication unknown: publisher unknown, undated.
  - Sunbeam Corporation, 1933-1988 (Box 37, Folder 12-14)
    Chicago Flexible Shaft Company. Kitchen Tested Recipes, Sunbeam Master, the King of Food Mixers. Chicago, IL: Chicago Flexible Shaft Company, 1933.
    Sunbeam Corporation. Sunbeam Mixmaster Junior. Chicago, IL: Sunbeam Corporation, 1952.
    Sunbeam. Sunbeam Controlled Heat Automatic Frypan. Chicago, IL: Sunbeam Corporation International, 1953.
    Sunbeam. New Sunbeam Special Cooker & Deep Fryer. Chicago, IL: Sunbeam Corporation, 1952.
    Chicago Flexible Shaft Company. How to Get the Most Out of Your Sunbeam Mixmaster. Chicago, IL: Chicago Flexible Shaft Company, undated.
    Sunbeam. Sunbeam Multi-Cooker Frypan. Chicago, IL: Sunbeam Corporation, undated.
    Oster. Oster Recipe Books. Milwaukee, WI: John Oster Manufacturing Co., undated.
    Sunbeam. Sunbeam Mixmaster Hand Mixer. Chicago, IL: Sunbeam Appliance Company, 1974.
  - Sunset Magazine, 1938 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    Sunset Magazine. Rich, Virginia, ed. Sunset's Western Hostess Guide. San Francisco, CA: Sunset Magazine, 1938.
  - Suntory International Corporation, circa 1980s (Box 37, Folder 16)
    Suntory International Corp. Imported Mohala Mango Liqueur. New York, NY: Suntory International Corp., undated.
  - Superintendent Royal Botanical Gardens of Trinidad--Bananas, 1887 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Swans Down Cake Flour, circa 1900 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Swanson, Alcoa, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    Swanson and Alcoa. Chicken Ideas by Swanson and Super Strength Alcoa Wrap. Place of publication unknown: publisher unknown, 1960.
  - Swift & Company, 1900-1908, circa 1950-1970s (Box 37, Folder 20, Box 38, Folder 1-2)
    Swift & Company. Visitors' Reference Book. Chicago, IL: Swift & Company, 1908.
    Swift & Company. Swift Illustrated. Chicago, IL: Swift & Company, undated.
    Swift & Co. How to Prepare Attractive Foods at Low Cost. Place of publication unknown: Swift & Company, undated.
    Swift & Co. The Buzzer. Place of publication unknown: Swift & Company, 1917.
    Swift & Co. Logan, Martha. "Mealtime Ideas" with Tender-Grown Swif's Premium Chicken. Place of publication unknown: Swift & Company, undated.
    Swift & Co. Logan, Martha. Fingertip Meals with Swift's Premium Canned Meats. Place of publication unknown: Swift & Company, undated.
    Swift & Co. Logan, Martha. Captivating Cookery with Allsweet. Place of publication unknown: Swift & Company, undated.
    Swift & Co. Logan, Martha. Foreign Food Ventures...American Style. Place of publication unknown: Swift & Company, undated.
    Swift & Company. Logan, Martha. All About Turkey Butterball Swift's Premium. Place of publication unknown: Swift & Company, undated.
    Swift & Company. Butterball Stuffed Turkey. Place of publication unknown: Swift & Company, 1979, by Butterball.
    Swift & Co. Logan, Martha. Patio Picnic Cook Book. Place of publication unknown: Swift & Company, undated.
    Swift & Co. Logan, Martha. Quick, Easy Meats for Round the Clock Meals. Place of publication unknown: Swift & Company, undated.
    Swift & Co. Logan, Martha. Recipes for Swift's Premium Bacon. Chicago, IL: Swift & Company, undated.
    Swift & Co. Logan, Martha. Your Favorite Swift's Premium Ham. Place of publication unknown: Swift & Company, circa 1955.
    Swift & Co. Logan, Martha. Our Best Hamburger Recipes. Place of publication unknown: Swift & Company, undated.
  - Swift and Copmany Research Laboratory, undated (Box 45, Folder 13)
    Danish Pastry; Puff Pastry
  - Swift Specific Company, 1891 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Sydney Howard Gay, circa 1840s-1880s (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - T. A. Faulds Company, Inc., 1920s (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Tanty, Francois, 1910 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - The T. A. Snider Preserve Company--Tomato Catsup, 1891 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Taylor Instrument Companies, 1921 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    Taylor Instrument Companies. Badenoch, Nena Wilson. Taylor Book of Recipes for Jelly Making, Canning and Preserving, Home Made Candy, Baking and Roasting. Rochester, NY: Taylor Instrument Companies, 1921.
  - Taylor Wine Company, Inc., 1965 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Taylor Wine Company. Come to Our Barbecue. Hammondsport, NY: Taylor Wine Company, 1965.
  - Technical Department of Bakers Weekly, 1923 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Texas Star Flour Mills, circa 1900 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    Texas Star Flour Mills. Ambrosia Cream of Wheat Tried Recipes. Galveston, TX: Texas Star Flour Mills, undated.
  - Thomas W. Emerson Company, 1926-1929 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Thorne, John, 1980, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Tiffin, New York; Tillamook County Creamery Association, circa 1910-1920s, 1935 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Tillamook County Creamery Association. Extra-Good Recipes Chosen from the Weekly Prize Contest Winners. Volume 9. Tillamook, OR: Tillamook County Creamery Association, undated.
    Tillamook County Creamery Association. New Tillamook Idea Book. Tillamook, OR: Tillamook County Creamery Association, undated.
  - T. Kingsford & Son, 1877, 1893, 1907 (Box 38, Folder 14-15)
    Kingsford. Lincoln, Mrs. D. A. Corn Starch Cookery: A Collection of Recipes for Dainty Dishes in which Kingsford's Oswego Corn Starch is a Principal Ingredient. Oswego, NY: T. Kingsford & Son., 1893.
    Kingsford. Hewitt, Emma Churchman. What A Cook Ought to Know about Cornstarch. Oswego, NY: T. Kingsford & Son, undated.
    Kingsford. Kingsford, T., & Son. Recipes for the Use of Kingsford's Oswego Corn Starch or Prepared Corn Manufactured by T. Kingsford & Son. Oswego, NY: R. J. Oliphant, Book and Job Printers, 1877.
    Kingsford. Hill, Janet M., and Alice Cary Waterman. Original Recipes and Cooking Help. Oswego, NY: T. Kingsford & Son, 1907.
  - T. M. Sinclair & Company, 1891 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Tomato Research, 1866-1920s, 1989-2003 (Box Shared Fales 002, Folder 15, Box 38, Folder 17, Folder 18)
    Mullen-Blackledge Co. "The Taste that Tell" Catsup, Chili Sauce and Soups. Indianapolis, IN: Mullen-Blackledge Co., undated.
    Palm Beach Groves. Leo & Paul's First Quality Vine-Ripe Tomatoes. Lantana, FL: Palm Beach Groves, undated.
  - Tomato Research--Campbell Soup Company; Joseph Campbell Company, 1917-1943 (Box Shared Fales 002, Folder 16)
  - Tomato Research--H. J. Heinz Company, 1925-1926 (Box Shared Fales 002, Folder 17)
  - Tousey, Frank, 1902 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Tru-Blu Biscuit Company, circa 1910-1920s (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Turkey Research, 1899-1945 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    Philips. Thanksgiving, 1899. (menu) Dayton, OH: The Phillips, 1899.
  - Tuskegee Normal & Industrial Institute, 1918-1942 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Union Starch & Refining Company--Pennant Syrups, circa 1910 - 1920s (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - United Fruit Company, 1904, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    Lawrence Company. A Short History of the Banana and a Few Recipes for its Use. Boston, MA: Chas. Lawrence Company, undated.
    United Fruit Company. Chiquita Banana's Recipe Book. New York, NY: United Fruit Company, 1950.
    United Fruit Company. Banana Recipes for Your Diet. New York, NY: United Fruit Company, undated.
  - United States Department of Agriculture--AIS-69, Money-Saving, 1948 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - United States Department of Agriculture--AIS-86, Dry Milk, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - United States Department of Agriculture-- Aunt Sammy's Radio Recipes, 1927 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - United States Department of Agriculture-- Aunt Sammy's Radio Recipes Revised, 1931 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - United States Department of Agriculture--Biological Survey, Bulletin No. 24, 1905 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - United States Department of Agriculture--Bulletin No. 1084, 1922 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - United States Department of Agriculture-- Farmers' Bulletin No. 200, No. 254, 1904, 1923 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    McGrew, T.F. "Turkeys: Standard Varieties And Management," Farmers' Bulletin No. 200. Washington, DC: United States Department of Agriculture, 1904.
  - United States Department of Agriculture-- Farmers' Bulletin No. 431, No. 751, 1916, 1917 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - United States Department of Agriculture-- Farmers' Bulletin No. 999, No. 1136, 1922, 1932 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    Miller, Fred E. "Sweetpotato Growing," Farmers' Bulletin No. 999. Washington, DC: United States Department of Agriculture, 1919. Revised 1932.
  - United States Department of Agriculture-- Farmers' Bulletin No. 1320, 1923 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - United States Department of Agriculture-- Farmers' Bulletin No. 1338, No. 1442, 1923, 1934 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    Thompson, H.C. "Storage of Sweetpotatoes," Farmers' Bulletin No. 1442. Washington, DC: United States Department of Agriculture, 1925. Revised 1934.
  - United States Department of Agriculture-- Farmers' Bulletin No. 1775, No. 1908, No. 1932, 1942, 1944 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    King, Florance B. with Adelle B. Freeman. "Homemade Bread, Cake and Pastry," Farmers' Bulletin No. 1775. Washington, DC: United States Department of Agriculture, 1937. Revised 1942.
  - United States Department of Agriculture-- Farmers' Bulletin No. 2011, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - United States Department of Agriculture-- Farmers' Bulletin No. 2063, 1954 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - United States Department of Agriculture-- Home & Garden Bulletin No. 40, No. 56, No. 243, 1954, 1958, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - United States Department of Agriculture--Leaflets No. 2, No. 66, No. 312, 1930, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    Yeatman, Fanny Walker and Mabel C. Stienbarger. "Rabbit Recipes," Leaflet No. 66. Washington, DC: United States Department of Agriculture, July 1930.
  - United States Department of Agriculture--New Mexico College, 1956 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - United States Department of Agriculture--Report on Maize, 1891 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - United States Department of Agriculture--University of California and Hilda Faust, circa 1940s (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - United States Department of Agriculture--War Food, 1944 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    United States Department of Agriculture, War Food Administration. Cut Food Waste: Make Food Fight for Freedom. Washington, DC: USDA, May 1944.
  - United States Department of Home Economics--Oven Canning, circa 1940 - 1950s (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - United States Department of the Interior--Tuna, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - United States Food Administration, 1917 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    United States Food Administration. War Economy in Food with Suggestions and Recipes for Substitutions in the Planning of Meals. Washington, DC: United States Food Administration, 1917.
  - United States Food Administration-- War Cook Book for American Women, 1917 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - United States House Committee on Interstate Commerce, circa 1950-1970s (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - United States House of Representatives, 21st Congress, 2nd Session--Document No. 55, No. 134: Brown & White Sugar, 1831 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - United States House of Representatives, 25th Congress, 3rd Session--Document No. 62: Beet Sugar, 1839 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Universal Cookery & Food Exhibition Honoris Causa Londoni Medal, 1901 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Universal Oyster Depot, 1880 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    Universal Oyster Depot with Henry E. Sterling, manager. All About Oysters; And How To Enjoy Them, Both In Their Natural Condition And Cooked. About 50 Recipes For Preparing The Same. Every Kind Of Oysters Can Be Obtained At The Lowest Possible Prices From The Universal Oyster Depot. London, England, UK: Universal Oyster Depot, 1880.
  - University of California--Apricots & Plums, 1922 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    Duruz, Willis P. "Harvesting And Handling Apricots And Plums For Eastern Shipment," Agricultural Experiment Station Circular No. 239. University of California, College of Agriculture, May 1922.
  - University of California, Berkeley--Avocado Industry, 1934 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    Hodgson, Robert W. "The California Avacado Industry," California Agricultural Extension Service Circular 43. Berkeley, CA: The College of Agriculture, University of California, April 1930, Revised September 1934.
  - University of Indiana--Isaac Smith and John Cook Bennett, undated, 1833 (Box Shared Fales 002, Folder 18)
  - University of Maine--Canning, 1935 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - University of Texas--Nuts, 1915 (Box 40, Folder 14)